{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who was the mastermind behind this masterpiece franchise?",
            "answers": ["Hideki Kamiya", "hideki kamiya"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What's the first thing Lady said to Dante when they met?",
            "answers": ["let me go!", "Let me go!"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Name of the city that worshipped Sparda?",
            "answers": ["Fortuna", "fortuna"]
        },
        {
            "question": "They waited for a long time for someone stronger than them, to help them in their journey",
            "answers": ["agni and rudra", "Agni and Rudra", "agni & rudra", "Agni & Rudra"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Her sacrifice split the family, once chose humanity while the other the demonic powers, she became a weapon for destruction",
            "answers": ["Kalina Ann", "kalina ann"]
        },
        {
            "question": "The brother explains the other brother what they are, wonder what he said what he is?",
            "answers": ["Nephilim", "nephilim"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Corrupted world of demons, parallel to ours but soo much different",
            "answers": ["Limbo", "limbo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Their mansion was quite the house of horror, Tony's Father was not a man to be reconned with - good that that idea got scraped",
            "answers": ["Lord Spencer", "lord spencer"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Tony Redgrave's one time partner , a shadow of the child of Sparda - alike yet so apart",
            "answers": ["Gilver", "gilver"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Need information? A middleman for your business? - I know just the guy, Just don't piss off the witch he's with",
            "answers": ["Enzo Ferino", "enzo ferino"]
        }
    ]
}